If you already have a draft, you've probably read it so many times at this
point that you don't know if it looks good and you don't know if it's
actually going to move the needle in a positive direction for you.
That's what these read and edit options are for.
Basically, you will give me a Google doc link to your essay or your essays,
and for each revision, I will send you back feedback within 48 hours.
I got into every college that I applied to, $600,000 in merit
scholarships and a full tuition scholarship to Vanderbilt because of
my college essays, and since then, I've worked with over a thousand
students directly, helping them write amazing essays that have gotten them
into schools like Penn, UC Berkeley with a Regent Scholarship, Dartmouth,
NYU, Cornell, and so many others.
And that is the exact strategy that I'm going to be applying
to your essay as I'm editing it.
So I will tell you what things to add to your essay.
I will reword some things for you if the grammar is off or the sentence
structure sounds bad, and I will make sure that you know exactly how to
tighten up each essay of yours so that it stands out and moves the needle
in a positive direction for you.
It's basically the same amount of expertise and guidance you would
get on a one-on-one call with me, except you don't have to have
the hassle of scheduling calls and trying to make time in your busy
schedule, especially if you're a senior dealing with a lot of things at once.
I offer a one-time edit on a single essay, or you can get packages of
edits, like multiple edits and revisions on your Common App Essay, multiple
edits on your supplementals, or I have an option for both.
Alternatively, if you just want one call of guidance with me, then I
also have a hybrid option where you can just do one call and then
get written edits after that.
If you feel completely stuck though, like you don't know where to start,
then that's where I would recommend that you book one of
my live one-on-one call options.
But if you already have stuff prepared and you just want to know if it's
good and make sure that it is ready to submit and it's going to move
the needle in a good direction for you, that's exactly what these
written edits are for, and I would love to help you.